Don't look away for even a second.
Every Secret Thing is a thriller, crime, mystery film directed by Amy J. Berg.
One clear summer day in a Baltimore suburb, a baby
goes missing from her front porch.
Two young girls serve seven years for the crime and are released
into a town that hasn't fully forgiven or forgotten.
Soon, another child is missing, and two detectives are called in to investigate
the mystery in a community where everyone seems to have a secret.
Helen Manning, played by Diane Lane.
Detective Nancy Porter, played by Elizabeth Banks.
Ronnie Fuller, played by Dakota Fanning.
Alice Manning, played by Danielle Macdonald.
Detective Kevin Jones, played by Nate Parker.
Devlin Hatch, played by Common.
Every Secret Thing is a 2014 American crime film directed by Amy J.
Berg and written by Nicole Holofcener, based on a 2004 novel
of the same name written by Laura Lippman.
The film stars Diane Lane, Elizabeth Banks, Dakota Fanning, Danielle Macdonald, and Nate Parker, and is
notable for being Academy Award-winning actress Frances McDormand's debut as producer.
The film was released theatrically on May 15, 2015
and on home video on August 4, 2015.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, kidnapping,
child murder, baltimore, usa, missing child.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.